What change can we have go back to slavery? I mean, these black millionaires that speak on
oppression and don't sacrifice their lives to step up to make change. Y'all all talk and part
of keeping us mentally enslaved in the past. Okay. So first of all, I have sacrificed a lot
of parts of my life. Uh, but more importantly, and I already blocked them. So that's why you
can't see the face, but more importantly, let me just, let me just lay something out for you real
quick. The way that capitalism is set up, if I was broke, you wouldn't listen to me either.
Y'all would say, I mean, you broke. What you going to tell us about change? You look like you on the
corner asking for change. Am I right? So let's cut it out. We know that in this nation, far too often,
we determine credibility by things that have nothing to do with actual insights and common
sense. If I was here talking about change, looking dusty and busted, y'all would be like,
Ooh, I want to hear about change from a brokey. Say I'm wrong.
Oh, niggas got me fucked up. Oh, niggas got me fucked up. Not today, not the one.